VERONIKA HARBACHOVA

Austin, TX | veronika.har@hotmail.com

Profile Summary

A passionate web developer with vast cross-cultural experience and a proven record of problem-solving and optimization skills. Highly keen on lean code, user-friendly intuitive layouts and responsive designs that look great on any screen size.

Education

Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development

CareerFoundry | 01/2019 - 11/2019

- 300+ hours of training/mentoring with industry leading Front-End and Senior Full-Stack Web Developer.
- Intensive project-based training program with a focus on Javascript, HTML, CSS and most prominent libraries, frameworks and tools;
- To see my skills in action, visit https://veronikaharbachova.netlify.com

MA in Linguistics

Dalian University of Technology | 09/2008 - 07/2011

BA in Linguistics

Belarusian State University | 09/2003 - 06/2008

Employment History

Wallenborn Transports S.A – Luxembourg, Luxembourg

Supply Chain Specialist | 02/2015 – 07/2016

- ✓ Provided customer service and account management for Qatar Airlines EU freight handling;
- ✓ Analyzed the company's internal S&OP software (AS-TRANS) and cooperated with an outsourced development team on its improvement;

Lear Corporation – Shanghai, China

Supply Chain Specialist | 11/2013 - 06/2014

- ✓ Lead Logistics Network Optimization for China Seating: identified potential of 20-25% (\$300k annually) savings;
- ✓ Supported LEAR Malaysia Supply Chain recovery;

Generation P – Minsk, Belarus

XSLT developer / Assistant Team-Leader | 09/2007 - 08/2008

- ✓ Achieved full technical competency in 3 months without any prior experience (CVS repo; PAROS (POST/GET); Oxygen+Eclipse; XML etc);
- ✓ Assistant Team-Leader supervised team performing patch-and-release responsibilities and negotiated business solutions with foreign customers.

Professional Skills

HTML

CSS

Javascript

Node.js

React.js

Redux

React Native

jQuery

APIs

Photoshop

Bootstrap

Responsive Design

TDD

Toolkit

NPM

TypeScript

Sass

Jest/Enzyme

CodePen

GitHub

Chrome Developer Tools

Soft Skills

Supportive

Empathetic

Approachable

Open-minded

Mission driven

Proactive

Adaptable

Collaborative

Open to feedback